<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="atom.xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://letdowntovoid.github.io/devlog-rse/blog</id>
    <title>My Site Blog</title>
    <updated>2025-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://letdowntovoid.github.io/devlog-rse/blog"/>
    <subtitle>My Site Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://letdowntovoid.github.io/devlog-rse/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orientation]]></title>
        <id>https://letdowntovoid.github.io/devlog-rse/blog/orientation</id>
        <link href="https://letdowntovoid.github.io/devlog-rse/blog/orientation"/>
        <updated>2025-08-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first BrainFlatulance. This shall be the term I intend to use to explain what's going on in my mind.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the first BrainFlatulance. This shall be the term I intend to use to explain what's going on in my mind.</p>
<p>For the project of course.</p>
<p>Now this would be the FIRST ever blog thing and this is where we are, and here are the prerequisites for you reader</p>
<admonition type="warning"><p>Remember, this is a devlog. Not a documentation. The main documentation will come out once I get close to release.</p><h3 id="so">SO,</h3><h1 id="do-not-complain-if-this-dev-log-is-unhinged-and-informal-i-do-this-to-keep-my-mind-empty-ok">DO NOT COMPLAIN IF THIS DEV LOG IS UNHINGED AND INFORMAL I DO THIS TO KEEP MY MIND EMPTY OK?</h1></admonition>
<!-- -->
<h1 id="you-gotta-know-these-things-before-you-read-this-devlog-thing">YOU GOTTA KNOW THESE THINGS BEFORE YOU READ THIS DEVLOG THING</h1>
<h3 id="this-is-my-devlog-mine">this is MY devlog. MINE</h3>
<h2 id="ok-this-is-my-devlog-letdowntovoids-yes-mine">OK? This is MY DEVLOG. letdowntovoid's YES MINE</h2>
<p>That means I will have fun and I will write this to my humour. Of course I will have tags to separate content from good ones to
stupid ones to serious ones. My tags should define how good an topic is.</p>
<h2 id="this-is-not-a-documentation">This is NOT a documentation.</h2>
<p>This is not a documentation of the project. This will just host my thoughts on what might happen and what is going on currently.
I don't like people who will refer to this as the documentation. No.</p>
<p><em>This is a STATEMENT from VoidWorks Inc. Ltd. GmbH. [FOR LEGAL REASONS THIS IS A JOKE AND I AM NOT REGISTERED PLEASE DON'T SUE ME]</em></p>
<h2 id="i-have-no-idea-when-this-project-will-complete-itself-or-what-am-i-doing">I have NO idea when this project will complete itself or what am I doing</h2>
<p>Seriously, I don't. I just came up with something impressive to impress the huzz B]</p>
<h2 id="i-would-love-every-single-bit-of-support-from-you-people-for-this-project-3">I would love every single bit of support from you people for this project &lt;3</h2>
<p>No seriously, I do. This project is something I am making while I learn so this will not be the best quality work. At all.
I would LOVE people joining me on this train and contribute with me on this project for the public. This is an abitiious project and you can join a development / miscellaneous server on Discord over at (this server)[<a href="https://discord.gg/F7yZJaRwS4">https://discord.gg/F7yZJaRwS4</a>].</p>
<p>I am not a very good developer and I will make mistakes so if you can help me test it feel free to join me!</p>
<h2 id="this-project-will-be-open-sourced-and-free-for-all-and-a-small-textwall">This project WILL be open sourced and free for all! [and a small textwall]</h2>
<p>As a developer who was on Roblox since 2016 (technically 2018 cause I actually stuck around after that), I loved Roblox. It gave me access to a massive community of some really REALLY good games.
I don't mean games that are cashgrabs I mean genuinely insanely fun games. I do not want to name any until I get their permission to but these games have allowed me to stick around on the platform and become a developer as well.
I understand that as we 25th of August, 2025, Roblox is recieving massive amounts of backlash with its course of actions on protecting their users and I have a feeling that the platform might not last.</p>
<p>This is why I am strongly moving forward with this project as well. I initially thought of this project back in 2020 but since I did not have much drive + I was not as good as I am today I was not ready to do this, but with recent circumstances I feel like I should
start something about this. That is why I want to make this project.</p>
<p>This project will be for everyone on the community and developers will <em>HOPEFULLY</em> be able to use the SDK to port over <code>rbxl</code> files into idk the game itself and run it as if its a standalone game. I have quite a bit to do and quite a bit to figure out but sure, I intend to do this over a few years.</p>
<h1 id="thats-a-small-sob-story-over">That's a small sob story over;</h1>
<p>but that describes why I wish to make this project.</p>
<p>How will I do it?</p>
<p>I have no <span class="spoiler"><span>fucking</span></span> idea.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>VoidWorks | LetDowntoVoid</name>
            <uri>https://google.com</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="Brain Flatulance (Horsing Aounr)" term="Brain Flatulance (Horsing Aounr)"/>
    </entry>
</feed>